If you can, check out the Marin County Arts Fair.
有机会不妨造访马林郡艺术节
It'll be going on through Thanks giving.
活动将持续到感恩节
Well, nothing's changed. We've got fog in the East Bay...
天气没有变化，在旧金山的东湾…
...and here in San Francisco.
云层低有雾
And We're looking at a high of 68 once these clouds burn off.
太阳破云而出时最高温68度
The time now is 23 after 7.
现在时刻7点23分
Oh, my gosh!
噢，天啊！
Hello!
哈罗！
Honey! Turn it off.
甜心！关掉！
We gotta make a baby.
我们得制造个宝宝
Yeah.
是啊
- I have an issue that... Resolved first. - We have an issue that needs resolving.
-我们有个问题--必须先解决 -我们才有个问题必须先解决
- Right now. - It's red.
-现在 -试纸是红的
Okay. I'll talk to you later. I thought you had a hearing.
我等会再跟你谈 我以为你要去听证会
I do. We've got 7 minutes for us, 15 for resting with my hips elevated...
没错，我们可以做爱7分钟 15分钟抬高臀部…
...and I'll only be 4 minutes late if there's no traffic.
如果没有堵车，我只会迟到四分钟
How about 10 for us, 12 for your hips?
做10分钟做爱 12分钟抬高行不行？
- 9 and 13. - Okay, deal. Come here.
-9跟13好了 -成交，上来吧
No, wait. It's supposed to work better if you're on top.
等等，你在上面效果比较好
I thought I'd never hear you say that. It's so nice.
我以为你都不愿意在下面
They said reduced sentence, but I can get a new trial.
他们提议减刑 但我可以安排一个重新审判
Claire, it's a first offense. We can ask for leniency.
这是初犯，试试要求从轻量刑
The forewoman's an advocate. She's not an impartial juror.
陪审团主席痛恨强暴犯 她的立场并不公正
This is a rape case. I don't Want to piss the judge off.
这是强暴案，我不想激怒法官
Trust me on this, Alex.
这事相信我，艾力克
Tell me you're joking.
告诉我你在开玩笑
Your Honor, my client is facing jail time...
庭上，我当事人面临被判刑…
...while they're laughing all the way to CNN.
检方却谈笑自若
- That's ridiculous. - Juror nine is a rape victim.
-荒谬至极 -9号陪审团员是强暴案受害者
And she's a fundraiser for a sexual assault hotline.
她积极筹募基金 赞助性侵害救助热线
The prosecution should have submitted that at the voir dire.
检方应该在宣誓时候就提出
- The misconduct does not stop there. - Oh, really?
-检方失职还不仅如此 -哦，是吗？
This office handled juror nine's case eight years ago...
这个法庭经办过9号陪审员的案子…
...and it's hard to believe no one recognized her.
我不相信没人认出她来
This is outrageous.
胡说八道
Do you feel justice was served?
你觉得司法公平吗？
We're pleased Gary Norris will get a new trial.
很高兴盖瑞诺里获得重新审判
His victim might say she's been raped by the system.
受害者可能说被制度二度强暴
My heart goes out to her.
我对她深表同情
But when a defendant's rights are violated, we are all at risk.
被告的权利被侵害 我们全部也都很危险
- Good job. - Thanks.
-漂亮 -谢谢
- Good job. I need to talk to you. - Good. I need gossip.
-做得好，我有话跟你说 -好，我喜欢八卦
- That was luck, you big... - Just like your Bruins last night.
-狗屎运，你这个-- -就像你昨晚的灰熊队
She scores again.
她又赢啦！
The heart of democracy beats on. Would you punch up my calendar?
拜民主制度之赐 行事历调出来，好吗？
- Personal or business? - Both. Thanks. Hi, big guy.
-私人还是公事？ -都要，谢谢
- Good work. We're proud of you. - Thank you very much.
-做得漂亮，我们以你为荣 -谢谢
I'll just type "partner" in right here, next to January 1.
我在元旦旁边写上“合伙人”
I didn't know you were clairvoyant.
我不知道你有千里眼
Really? Are you serious?
真的吗？说真的？
We'll see.
等着瞧罗
Not bad. I think that was just lucky.
不赖嘛，我觉得那只是运气
- Bring it on, girl. - Pretty.
-很酸哦 -漂亮
- Pretty nice. - Pretty lucky. Well...
-运气好，但是…
- I'm taking you to pool school. - You don't have a shot.
-我要带你去撞球学校多学着点 -没一颗会进
- 15 off the 5 in the corner pocket. - Not in this lifetime.
-15号进底袋 -门都没有
That is not fair. That is not fair!
不公平，不公平
No, you can't use your left hand now.
现在禁止用左手
You are a mutant.
你是基因突变人
Hey, look.
嘿，你们看
- This Was City Hall today. - Do you feel justice Was served?
-这是今天在市政府外的情形 -你觉得司法公平吗？
We're pleased Gary Norris...
很高兴盖瑞诺里…
Oh, my gosh!
噢，天啊
You look great!
你真漂亮
Look at you!
看看你
- We are all at risk.
我们也全部很危险
Any comments for the family?
对那家人有何建议？
Honey. Lock the door. Someone's in the house.
亲爱的，门锁上 房子里有人
- Hurry! - Wait up!
-快！ -等等！
Damn kids.
该死的小鬼
It's okay, honey.
没事了，他们走了
25 Dover. Send somebody right away. Are you okay?
多佛25号，马上派人过来 你没事吧？
Oh, God.
噢，天啊
I'm fine.
我没事
- How old is he? - Fourteen months.
-他多大？ -14个月
Uh-oh, baby alert.
哦，有个小孩
Hi. Could we meet your baby?
嗨，可以看看他吗？
Hi! Oh, my God, what a doll.
天啊，好可爱哟
He's in a pretty good mood.
他心情很好
He doesn't have on a T-shirt or something.
他连一件T恤也没穿
The movie was a huge hit. Men all across America quit buying T-shirts.
那部电影大卖 全美所有的人都不再买T恤了
Oh, is it like It's a Wonderful Life?
那部片好像叫“甜美的生活”
Nice. Christmas domestic. Yeah, that's the spirit.
好极了，圣诞节家庭纠纷 这才是精神所在
Interesting. Real interesting.
有趣，真有趣
IKeys, please.
钥匙给我
What is it, babe?
怎么回事？
FBI! Get down!
FBI！趴下！
Get down! Get down!
趴下！…
Get down! On the ground! On the ground, now!
趴下！趴在地上！ 现在就趴在地上！
Stop! Leave her alone!
住手！放开她！
- You screwed up the whole thing. - You're looking at a lawsuit, Mulkins.
-你搞砸了 -你等着挨告吧，穆金先生
Harassment. Reckless endangerment.
骚扰，枉顾公共安全
It's Mullins, Mrs. Ikubik. Special Agent Mullins.
我叫穆林，裘毕太太 穆林特别探员
You have a warrant for Ron Chapman.
你要拘捕的人叫朗查普曼
My husband is Tom Ikubik. Your computer is psychotic.
我先生名叫汤姆裘毕 你的电脑发神经了
It wasn't our computer. If you had gotten any closer...
不是我们电脑的错 你们要是再靠近一点…
...you would have burned the guy, all right? Fine, forget about it.
会把他活活烧死，知道吗？ 算了
It was Marin P.D. They ran the prints after your house was burglarized.
是马林警方 你们遭闯空门后他们调出指纹档案
They flagged your husband's. They've been in the system for 12 years.
查出你先生的指纹建档已12年
- What is he being accused of? - Sorry, I can't tell you.
-请问他犯了什么罪？ -我不能说
Oh, come on. I have the right to know the charges.
我有权知道罪名
Not when it's a military court or when national security is involved.
不，在军事法庭 事关国家安全便无权知道
Military court?
军事法庭？
Thank God I caught you. I was afraid you'd be out of town.
还好找到你了 我很担心你出门去了
I caught you on the news. Stop letting them mess with your hair.
我在电视上看到你 别让他们乱搞你的头发
- Jackie? - I need money. I hate to ask.
-贾姬？ -我需要钱，虽然很不想开口
Well, not really. Can you just help me out?
既然说了，可以帮个忙吗？
My landlord's breathing down my neck. If you say no, I'll be evicted.
房东逼得紧，快被扫地出门了
Can you come get me?
你可以来接我吗？
I know what it is. Maybe he did something he doesn't know he did.
我知道是怎么回事 可能是他无意中做了什么事
- And so he... - That's enough.
-所以他-- -别再说了
- No, but he's in witness protection... - Just stop it.
-或许他是被保护的证人-- -拜托别瞎猜
Sorry. Next time you need help, call your other sister.
对不起，下次有麻烦找其他姐妹
Oh, wait, you don't have another sister.
哦，你没有其他姐妹
You called me, Jackie.
是你打给我的，贾姬
I picked you up. It's the first time you've tried to see me in months.
我来接你，这是这几个月来 你第一次想见我
The base is in San Lazaro, 45 minutes south of L.A.
基地在洛城南方 45分钟车程的圣拉萨罗
I booked you a flight into Orange County.
我帮你订了飞橘郡的机票
- Okay, With luggage? - You should be on the base by 11:30.
-带行李吗？ -11点半可以到基地
Good afternoon. May I see your I.D.?
午安，请出示证件
All right.
好
Mrs. Ikubik. James Hernandez. Ron and I were in the same unit.
裘毕太太？詹姆士贺南德兹 跟朗同单位
This must be a shock. If there's anything I can do...
你一定大受震惊 如果能帮上任何忙…
Atchison, Chapman, Green.
艾契生、查普曼、葛林
Ron was a good Marine. I won't keep you. Good luck.
朗是位好军人 不耽搁你了，祝你好运
- Thank you. - At the end of the hall, ma'am.
-谢谢 -在大厅尽头，女士
Room B, ma'am.
B室，女士
What the...?
什么--？
- Where are his clothes? - Suicide watch.
-他的衣服呢？ -预防他自杀
Put clothes on him now!
马上帮他穿上衣服
You'd have to file that request with the brig command.
你可以向狱方提出申请
Is your name Ron Chapman?
你的名字叫朗查普曼？
Yes.
是的
I don't know what to say.
我不知道该说什么
I had no choice.
我身不由己
I had no...
我…. 身不由己
They were accusing me of something that I didn't do. Please believe me.
他们给我乱扣罪名 请相信我
Believe you?
相信你？
Well, I believed that you were raised in a foster home.
我相信你在寄养家庭长大
- I was. - That you were never married.
-的确是啊 -你从没结过婚
That you don't have any children. That you loved me, Ron.
你没有孩子，你爱我，朗
Tom? Whatever your name is.
汤姆？天晓得你叫什么名字
I do love you, but I did not do this.
我真的爱你，但不是我干的
I swear that I never did this.
我发誓不是我干的
And I didn't want to tell you because I didn't want you to leave me.
我没有跟你说 是因为我不要你离开我
What happened?
到底发生了什么事？
My lawyer's here.
我的律师来了
Mrs. Ikubik?
裘毕太太？
Sorry to interrupt. First Lieutenant Embry, Terrence.
抱歉打扰，我是泰伦斯恩比中尉
I'm older than I look. So...
我只是看起来比较年轻…
Well, I'll let you twos... I'll wait in the...
你们两位先…. 我可以等…
Claire.
克莱儿
Just let me go talk to him, okay?
让我跟他谈谈，好吗？
First lieutenant? Is that what I call you?
该称呼你中尉吗？
Lieutenant.
中尉
Why haven't you filed a request to get him out of those chains?
为什么不申请让他不带手铐？
I'll take care of it.
我会去办
I'm an attorney. May I see the charging document?
我是律师，起诉书可以看吗？
- We call it a charge sheet. - Fabulous. May I see it?
-我们称之为起诉单 -很好，我可以看吗？
- Can you give me the basics? - Article 85, desertion.
-能不能简略解释一下？ -85条：逃兵
Article 90, willfully disobeying a superior officer...
90条：蓄意攻击或违抗长官…
Murder? Nine...
谋杀？九--
Yes. If convicted, he'll get the death penalty.
对，定罪的话是死刑
Who's prosecuting?
谁负责起诉？
Major Lucas Waldron has been detailed as trial counsel.
法官裁定卢卡司华仲少校
- He any good? - The best.
-他厉害吗？ -顶尖高手
- How about you? - I do okay.
-那你呢？ -还过得去
- Have you ever won a case? - No.
-曾胜诉过吗？ -不曾
I'm going to defend you. I know you didn't kill 9 people.
我要替你辩护，你没谋害九条命
- Mrs. Ikubik... - I don't want you involved.
-裘毕太太-- -我不希望你介入此事
- I'm already involved. - Military law is not the same...
-我已经介入了 -军法是不一样的--
I'll learn. We're gonna fight them, okay? Together.
我可以学 我们向他们合力宣战
You remember those three American kids?
记得那三个美国学生吗？
Students Who Were killed in that cafe in El Salvador in '88.
88年在萨尔瓦多咖啡店 被杀的学生
Not in the camera, man.
不要拍摄
It Was a little toWn called Monte Azul.
一个叫蒙特亚萨的小镇
A member of a rebel group threW a satchel bomb into that cafe.
反抗团体向店内掷包裹炸弹
- Press had a field day. - Right. Everybody went nuts.
-媒体大肆报导 -对，群情哗然
So they call up my unit, Detachment 27, to locate the rebel leader.
他们要我们单位，27特遣队 去找出反抗团体的头子
- A terrorist named Danilo Chacon. - And your orders came from...?
-一个叫丹尼洛夏康的恐怖份子 -你的命令是来自…？
Our C.O. At Camp Lejeune, Bill Marks. Anyways...
勒穹基地指挥官比尔马克--
Wait. I'm sorry. Brigadier General Marks?
等等，对不起，是马克准将？
Representative to the Congressional Committee...
国会军事委员会的…
...on Military Appropriations. Bill Marks?
特别代表，比尔马克？
Yes. He was Colonel Bill Marks back then.
是的，当时还是比尔马克上校
Under his orders, we were sent in to a little village called Las Colinas.
经他下令 我们被送到拉斯柯林纳村
It's not even a village, even. Just some fields, a feW huts.
甚至不算村子，只是田和草寮
Danilo Chacon was supposed to be hiding out there and...
据报丹尼洛夏康藏匿在那里…
It was supposed to be routine.
本来只是例行公事
But somebody lost it.
不料却有人失控了
I hear a gun fire.
我听到枪声
By the time I get to the other end of the village, 9 people are slaughtered.
等我赶到村子另一头时 九条人命已遭屠杀
I'm just standing there. Old women, men, kids, just dead, and I lost it.
我站在哪儿，老妇人 男人、小孩才刚气绝，我气疯了
I jumped the guy who did it.
于是攻击行凶者
And next thing I know, I'm looking at first-degree, nine specs.
接下来，我被控一级谋杀 九条人命
- Who did it? - Hernandez. Jimmy Hernandez.
-谁干的？ -贺南德兹，吉米贺南德兹
He ordered me to keep my mouth shut. Said Marks Would back him up.
他命令我闭嘴 他说马克会挺他
- I told him to go to hell. - Major Hernandez, Marks' top aide?
-我说他会遭天谴 -贺南德兹少校？马克头号助手
He introduced himself to me yesterday in the waiting area.
昨天他还在等候室向我自我介绍
What?
什么？
Claire, listen. I want you to stay away from him.
克莱儿，听我说，离他远点
He's extremely dangerous, do you understand?
他非常危险，明白吗？
So General Marks... See, he's like the most decorated, most powerful...
马克将军受勋无数…
And you're saying you were framed by General Marks and his assistant?
而你说你被马克将军 和他的特别助理诬陷
That's our defense?
这是我们的辩护内容？
Yep.
对
I'm not looking forward to the firm's name being remotely connected to this.
我不愿公司跟此事有任何牵连
As it stands now, nobody knows Ron Chapman is Tom Ikubik.
现在还没人知道 朗查普曼就是汤姆裘毕
- My husband's innocent. - I'm sure he is.
-我丈夫是无辜的 -当然
I'm not interested in seeing his name associated with murder.
我当然不愿见他扯上重大命案
I just want you to understand all the possible, unforeseen consequences.
我只是要你了解一切可能的后果
I'll make it easy for you. If the firm gets dragged into this, I'll resign.
我不会为难你 若牵连到公司，我会请辞
Josh, remember that thing from the...?
乔许，记得那件事--？
- Thank you. - Claire, can I do anything?
-谢谢 -我可以帮什么忙吗？
Yeah. I need a lawyer. Somebody from the Marine Corps.
我需要一位陆战队出身的律师
Somebody who can beat them.
曾打败过军方的
Where will you be?
你会在哪里？
Bill. Bill. William.
账单，账单，张丹
I'm looking for a Charlie Grimes.
我找查理葛莱
Don't tell me you need a lawyer, because you are one.
别告诉我你需要一个律师 因为你自己就是个律师
I followed the Norris case. Talk about a rabbit out of a hat.
我有注意诺里一案，你很神嘛
Are you Charles W. Grimes?
你就是查理葛莱？
You can't get over my decorator, can you? Welcome to Grimes & Associate.
我的装潢你很不适应吧？ 欢迎光临葛莱联合事务所
Associate?
联合事务所？
Delilah?
黛利拉？
Rumor has it you're a good attorney. Formerly of the J.A.G. Corps.
有人推荐你 你曾在高署检察官那儿工作
In another life.
上辈子的事啦
You had an affair with your superior officer's wife...
你和长官之妻有染--
Let's not dwell on my youthful offenses. What do you want?
好汉不提当年勇，什么事？
The military set up my husband...
我丈夫遭军方诬陷…
...and assigned a junior varsity lieutenant to defend him.
他们指派个菜鸟中尉为他辩护
- Who's prosecuting? - Waldron.
-谁负责起诉？ -华仲
He should cop a plea. Try to make a deal.
叫你丈夫认罪，请求从轻发落
Military justice is to justice as military music is to music. Wake up.
如果军歌也算音乐 军法也是种司法
Charlie, you're not gonna believe this. They busted me again.
查理，说你也不会相信 我又被捕了！
It's like every time I turn around, they slap handcuffs on me.
好像每次我一不留神 就被拷上手铐
Every time you turn around, you've got some private's privates.
因为你一不留神 就跟大兵瞎搞
I perform an important service for the military.
我为军队提供特别服务
There's a novel defense.
这真是新兴的辩护
- You do somebody at the base too? - Yeah, actually.
-你也搞上了基地里的人？ -也算是吧
- Is your lawyer here any good? - When he gets off his ass, yeah.
-你的律师厉不厉害？ -发起飙来挺厉害的
How about it, Mr. Grimes?
我的案子接不接，葛莱先生？
- Man, turn this shit off. - Nice to meet you.
-不要看电视啦 -幸会
- I'm due in court in an hour. - An hour!
-一小时后开庭 -一小时！
Jackie.
贾姬？
I'm here to help, 'cause what are sisters for?
我来帮你，姐妹不是作假的
Wow. Tacky.
哇，好俗哦
You got evicted, didn't you? What happened to the money I sent?
还是被踢出来了，对吗？ 我汇去的钱呢？
Too little, too late. I need an extra phone line.
不够也太晚了 我需要多装一条电话线
- What for? - My new job. Psychic hotline.
-为什么？ -新工作，通灵热线
Don't laugh. I'm really good at it.
别笑，我很在行的
It's 29 past the hour if you're on your Way to Work.
已经29分了 如果你要去上班的话
OtherWise kick back, I got you covered.
否则大可放松心情
- Good morning.
-早安
I'm gonna kill that goddamn clock.
我要把那个闹钟砸了
- Hey, GI Joe. - Ma'am.
-嗨，阿兵哥 -你好，女士
Ma'am? Claire, did you hear that? He just called me "ma'am."
听到没？你听到了吗？ 他称我为“女士”
- Shall we? - Yeah, let's get out of here.
-可以走了吗？ -我们走吧
I don't need security clearance for the pretrial?
所以审判前我不需要经过安全检查？
The only portions that are classified...
对，审判中的机密文件…
...are those pertaining to the incidents in El Salvador.
只跟萨尔瓦多事件有关
You know, I hope she didn't think I was staring.
希望她没误会我盯着她看
- Who? - Well, your sister.
-谁？ -你妹妹
Oh, don't worry about it. She understands. She's psychic.
别担心，她是通灵大师
Well, what do you know? Mr. Grimes has decided to join us.
知道吗？葛莱先生要加入我们
You do know that Charlie Grimes has a history of being a major drunk?
你知道查理葛莱曾经是个酒鬼吗？
Are you sober, Mr. Grimes?
你清醒吗？葛莱先生
Four hundred and sixty-two days, Mrs. Ikubik. Ain't life grand?
戒酒462天了，裘毕太太 生活多美好啊？
- Fill me in. - Pretrial hearing is in 10.
-案情提要 -10分后举行开审前公听
- Ten what? - Minutes.
-10什么？ -10分钟
What?
怎么？
You don't think they'll be impressed with leather?
他们不喜欢皮衣吗？
- Who's the judge? - Colonel Farrell.
-法官是谁？ -法罗上校
It would be.
我猜也是
Full-bird colonel at his terminal rank.
再也升不了官的资深上校
He'll piss on us because we're civilians.
他藐视我们平民百姓
And he won't give a shit about reversals because he's retiring.
根本不担心别人上诉 因为退休在即
File any motions?
你想提什么请求？
Dismissal of charges, insufficient evidence.
罪证不足，无罪开释
- Motion denied. - You haven't read it.
-一定被否决 -你还没看呢
Neither has Farrell. The military judicial system is based on denial.
我怀疑法罗也没看 军法体制以否决为基础
- Then we fight the system. - No, no, no, no.
-那我们就挑战体制 -不，不，不
You play by the rules. Do not fight the system.
照体制内的游戏规则 挑战体制必输无疑
You fight the system, you lose. Isn't that right, Embry?
挑战体制必输，对吧，恩比？
Say, "Yes, sir."
说“是的，长官”
Don't be a sap, Embry. Nobody in a uniform can think for himself.
唯唯诺诺 穿制服的不能为自己着想
This is a pretrial hearing. The goal is to not reveal anything.
这是审前公听，我们多听少说
Do we have anything to reveal, Mrs. Ikubik?
我们有得说吗，裘毕太太？
- No. - No? Then that ought to work.
-没有 -没有？那只好多听少说罗
- Which one's the prosecutor? - We call them trial counsels.
-哪位是检察官？ -军中称他们为审议律师
- Mrs. Ikubik, I'm Major Waldron. - How do you do?
-裘毕太太，我是华仲少校 -你好吗？
Hi, Lucas.
嗨，卢卡司
- Charlie Grimes. Nice to see you. - Bullshit.
-查理葛莱，真高兴再见面 -虚情假意
All rise.
起立
Be seated. This article 39A session is called to order.
请坐，39A庭现在开始
I'm Colonel Farrell, U.S. Marine Corps.
本人陆战队上校法罗
Where the hell's the accused?
被告呢？
Charlie Grimes.
查理葛莱
I'll explain later.
待会再解释
Sergeant Chapman, how do you plead?
查普曼上士，请提出申辩？
We have a motion to have all charges dismissed.
我们请求撤销所有控诉
Motion denied. In the court-martial system, we don't have clients.
否决，你对军事法庭十分生疏 这里没有所谓当事人
Sergeant Ron Chapman is the accused, and I'm still waiting for the plea.
查普曼是被告，我要他申辩
I plead not guilty. Not guilty.
我自认无罪 无罪
You may be seated.
你可以坐下了
We request a ruling on the permissibility...
检方请求庭上裁决…
...of the accused being represented by his spouse.
被告配偶是否能为之辩护
- Your Honor... - I'll allow it.
-庭上-- -我准许
Thank you, Your Honor.
多谢庭上
We request a short pretrial period to ensure security.
为顾及安全请求缩短审前期限
Granted. Opening statements are in a week.
同意，一周后开始审判
Objection. We can't prepare a defense for a capital case in one week.
抗议，重大刑案一周太仓促
Overruled. Are we done?
驳回，还有其他意见吗？
We have no intention of waiving our right to a public trial...
根据宪法第六修正案…
...as guaranteed by the Sixth Amendment.
被告声明无意放弃公开审判权
This case involves national security.
此案攸关国家安全
Any attempt to try this case in the media would violate this court's order.
任何想在媒体前审理这个案子的企图 会破坏这个法庭的秩序
As civilians, we are not subject to military orders.
身为平民 我们不受军方命令约束
Any such orders will be taken for informational purposes only.
任何命令皆仅供参考
Civilian or not...
平民与否…
...you can be disqualified from participating in this trial.
可能会丧失继续辩护的资格
All rise.
起立
And so it begins. See you soon.
开始打仗啦 回头见
He's supposed to be the best.
听说他是一流高手
What the hell was that?
你发什么神经？
I said you should follow the rules. I'm the wild card.
我说你当乖乖牌 我可以不按牌理出牌
- We could get thrown off the case. - It's too early.
-他可以取消我们的资格 -时候未到
If they think we'll go public, we get an idea how scared they are.
如果他们知道我们可能公诸于世 他们可紧张了
What do you think?
你觉得呢？
I think, why me? Why was I assigned to this case?
我觉得为何是我？ 这个案子为何指派给我？
Seven guys in Tom's unit, and all of them say he did it.
汤姆的单位有七个人 全都说是他干的
But only two witnesses are on their list.
但只有两人列入证人名单
Hernandez and Abbott. What about the rest?
贺南德兹和阿巴，其他人呢？
Dead.
死了
- All of them? - Dead how?
-全死了？ -怎么死的？
Two were killed in combat. One was murdered...
两个死于战场 一个被谋杀
...and the other two, accidents.
两个出意外
Accidents?
意外？
I know a couple PI's. Ex-Green Berets.
我认识几个私家侦探，前绿扁帽
Maybe they could get us the unofficial version of how these guys died.
或许可以打听到非官方版本 有关他们的真正死因
Could be useful.
说不定有帮助
Here we go. Troy Abbott in Sacramento.
特洛阿巴在沙加缅度
Doing four to six in Lompoc, armed robbery.
在隆帕克服刑，持枪抢劫
And Waldron's office is trying to expedite his parole.
华仲积极帮他申请假释
Why do I know he'll succeed?
我为什么知道他一定会成功？
Because it's the Marines. "Be all you can be."
因为陆战队“攻无不克”
That's the Army.
那是陆军的广告词
Mrs. Ikubik, I really think our theory should be that Hernandez acted alone.
裘毕太太，我觉得我们应该咬定 贺南德兹独自行动
No one's gonna believe Marks was in on this.
没人会相信马克将军涉案
In other words, you don't believe it.
意思是你也不相信
- That's not my point. - Do you believe Tom or not?
-这不是重点 -你到底相不相信汤姆？
Easy. He's just expressing his opinion.
别激动，他只是表达意见
Shouldn't you be somewhere else?
你不是有别的事要忙？
Not really.
不急
- Can I get you another coffee, sir? - No, ma'am. I'm good.
-再来一杯咖啡吗，先生？ -不用，女士，我够了
I'll have to agree with Embry. I like Marks.
我同意恩比，我喜欢马克
Smells, looks, tastes credible. He'll just give Hernandez credibility.
浑身散发出公信力 他若作证对贺南德兹反而有利
- That's what I'm saying. - He's had an original thought.
-我就是这个意思 -年轻人蛮有创意的
- Go to hell. - Another one.
-你去死吧 -这也是创意
- Can you hold for Major Waldron? - Yes, I'll hold for Major Waldron.
-华仲少校找你，请稍等 -好，我等他
- Hello, Mrs. Kubik. - Hello, major.
-你好，裘毕太太 -你好，少校
Come doWn to my office. We'll try to Work something out.
请到我办公室来协商协商
We'll be there.
没有问题
I can't believe it. They want a deal.
真不敢相信他们想协商
I love being a wild card.
所以我喜欢不按牌理出牌
Mr. Ikubik, voluntary manslaughter, only one specification.
裘毕太太，只有一样控诉 蓄意杀人
That's only five years.
只关五年
Plus one condition that you sign a nondisclosure agreement?
外加一纸秘密协定？
As your counsel...
身为你的辩护律师--
Claire, tell the man to take the deal of the century.
叫他接受千载难逢的好机会
Sweetheart?
亲爱的？
I won't do five minutes for a crime I didn't commit.
五分钟冤狱我都不愿意做
Do you have any idea...
你们知不知道…
...what it's like to spend 23 hours a day in a 6-by-8 cell?
一天23小时关在鸟笼的滋味？
Five years. They'll make sure I'm dead long before that.
不用关五年就被他们弄死了
So motion denied?
所以提议否决？
Come on in. Based on our...
请进，根据--
That's all right. We're here to tell you we're gonna pass.
不用了，少校，我们无法接受
Thanks anyway.
还是谢谢你
Mrs. Ikubik.
裘毕太太
I'm happy to go to trial with this case.
我个人倒是赞成进行审判
Putting this behind us works for everyone. Command and your husband.
让这个结束 对指挥官和你丈夫都有利
And Major Hernandez and General Marks. See you in court, sir.
还有贺南德兹少校和马克将军 法庭上见
- Here on the Fantasy Jewelry Hour. - I'd expect to pay $ 199 for this.
-这是梦想珠宝频道 -我只愿意出一百九十九元
Yes, you Would. This beautiful piece is available...
是的 这个漂亮的珠宝…
So no deal. Can you believe I asked my husband to do five years in prison?
不可能，你相信我竟然企图 叫我老公坐五年牢？
Go ahead. Tell me what a waste of oxygen all lawyers are.
说律师的良心都被狗吃了
If you're on the phone noW, don't get off the line.
如果你在电话上 先不要挂
- That's right. - You Won't Want to miss this.
-对 -你不会想错过这个
You're curiously quiet on the subject.
你安静得很诡异哦
Jackie, would you please turn that down?
贾姬，关小声一点，好吗？
Your husband came to my village and killed my family. And it's true:
你丈夫滥杀我家人和村民
Lawyers are a waste of oxygen. Drop this deal...
律师的确都死没良心是真理 放弃本案--
Excuse me? Mrs. Ikubik.
裘毕太太？
He ran out.
他跑出去了
Claire. Claire, are you okay?
克莱儿，你没事吧？
Bastards!
王八蛋！
It's Hernandez. Oh, goddamn.
是贺南德兹，可恶
We turned down their deal, and he's trying to scare us.
我们拒绝协商，他想吓我们
You don't know how they work.
你不了解他们的手段
- I don't know how any of it works. - What do you mean?
-这些手段我一无所知 -什么意思？
- This other life of yours. - You don't believe me, do you?
-你另一个身分的生活 -你不相信我？
- Of course I believe you. - Baby, I'll take a polygraph.
-当然相信 -我愿意接受测谎
No need. It's not admissible in court.
它不能作为呈堂供证
The hell with the courts. I want to do it for us.
不管法庭，只证明给你看
Hey, Ronnie. Or Tommy or whatever. You haven't changed.
朗尼，或汤米，你一点都没变
- This is an unethical ex parte. - I'm here to help.
-这是不道德的 -我想帮点忙
- What are you doing here? - You ought to plead this out.
-你来干嘛？ -你该接受我们的条件
Stop it! Stop!
汤姆，住手
You're making it worse!
你会越弄越糟！
Who let him in here? He is not authorized to be in here!
谁让少校进来的？ 他不能进来
- He is provoking my client! - Look at your killer!
-他向我当事人挑衅！ -看看你的凶手
Who let him in? He's not supposed to be in here!
谁让他进来的？ 他不该进来！
- He said he was a defense witness. - He is not!
-他自称是辩方证人 -他不是辩方证人！！
Who is in charge? I want to talk to whoever is in charge.
谁是主管？我要跟你们主管谈谈
- Is your real name Ron Chapman? - Yes.
-你真名叫朗查普曼？ -是的
Regarding the incident at Las Colinas on March 15, 1988...
你愿意据实回答 发生在1988年3月15日的…
...will you answer my questions truthfully?
拉斯柯林纳事件吗？
Did you participate in the death of anyone...
你是否主动引发该项…
...during the March 15, 1988 shootings?
发生在1988年3月15日的杀戮事件？
Mrs. Ikubik?
裘毕太太？
- You passed. - Of course I passed.
-你通过测谎了 -我当然通过
- Are we being monitored? - No, it's absolutely secure.
-我们被监视着吗？ -没有，绝对安全
Absolutely secure?
绝对安全？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
What do you think I mean?
你认为呢？
And lieutenant colonel...
中校…
...were there any eyewitnesses to this massacre?
这次屠杀有目击证人吗？
Yes. We had seven eyewitness statements, all I.D. Ing Chapman.
有，七位证人全都指认查普曼杀人
Thank you.
谢谢
Nothing further, Your Honor.
我问完了，庭上
Colonel LaPierre, you were and still are a special agent with...
拉皮耶中校 你目前还是担任本案的…
...the criminal investigations division in charge of this investigation?
罪案调查单位的特派员，对吗？
That's correct.
对
So when you say the investigation was not flawed...
你说本案的调查毫无瑕疵
...you're giving yourself a big thumbs up.
你对自己评价很高罗？
- I'm just expressing my opinion. - So help you God, no doubt.
-我只不过是表达意见 -当然了
Now, is it possible, colonel, that these so-called witnesses...
现在请问 中校，有没有可能这些证人…
...were coached before you talked to them?
事前接受过某种指令？
I guess it's possible, but unlikely.
有此可能，但我相信没有
Are you aware that of the seven witnesses...
你知不知道七人中…
...two were subsequently killed in combat?
两人后来死于战场？
I'm aware of that.
我知道
And another three, three relatively young men, have died as well?
其他三位相当年轻的男人 也相继死亡？
- Yes. - Let's see.
-知道 -我们来看看
There was a Lt. Allen of Longview, Texas. Hit-and-run.
亚伦中尉，在德州车祸殒命 肇事者逃逸
A Sgt. Stenstrom of Taos, New Mexico. Accidental drowning.
史丹斯壮上士 意外溺毙于新墨西哥州
The other, an unfortunate mountain climbing fall.
另一位登山发生不幸
- That sounds right. - Does it?
-听起来没错 -是吗？
Well, that's interesting, colonel...
有趣的是，中校…
...seeing as how I just made up those causes of death.
这些死因是我捏造的
There was no accidental drowning and no mountain climbing fall.
没有意外溺毙 也没有登山意外
I have the details of these deaths, including a home-invasion robbery...
我有死因的详细资料 包括一桩闯空门抢劫…
...if you care to look at them.
你要不要过目一下？
I'm fuzzy on the details. I didn't lead those investigations.
我对于这些死因不很清楚 这些调查不是我负责的
No further questions.
我问完了
- My investigation was... - No further questions.
-我的调查是-- -质问完毕
Hello?
喂？
You knoW the Witness in Tom's unit Who Was murdered?
你知道被谋杀的那位证人？
- Home-invasion robbery. - He Was killed in front of his Wife.
-遭强盗闯空门那位 -他在妻子面前被杀
The Word is, she accused the military of having been involved.
据说她指控军方难脱关系
Will she talk to us?
她愿意跟我们谈吗？
Problem there is that she disappeared right after that.
问题是她从那时就失踪了
- Is this a bad time? - Bad time? No.
-我来错时间了 -来错时间？不会
We could go over the Hernandez cross.
我们该再看看贺南德兹的证词
I was taking a break...
我才刚休息…
...because I was going over the Hernandez stuff myself, and...
因为之前在研究他的资料--
Don't be mad. It wasn't him. It was all me.
别发火，不是他，我主动的
This doesn't affect anything, okay? My work. I'm totally up for it.
这不会影响办案 我准备好了，蓄势待发
He is. Come on, Claire. We were just going over his briefs.
他说得没错 我们正准备作重点突破
- Claire, wait. - You never take anything seriously.
-克莱儿，等一下嘛 -你从来就没个正经
Oh, yeah. That's right.
噢，是的，就是这样
You get to be the lawyer, so I gotta get to bang one, right?
你是个律师 我只能搞上个律师，对吗？
Closed.
打烊了
- Sorry, we're closed. - Excuse me.
-我们打烊了 -对不起
- How do I get to State Street? - Two blocks down.
-我怎么去时代街？ -再过两个街口
- Thank you. - Sorry.
-谢谢 -对不起
Want some cheese?
要买起士吗？
- Yeah, I could make an omelette. - I'll make one.
-好啊，我可以做煎蛋饼 -我来做
- You want cheddar? American? Swiss? - Cheddar's good.
-切达的？美国的？瑞士的？ -切达的
Mrs. Chapman?
查普曼太太？
It's Ikubik.
我姓裘毕
I wanna tell you about what I do for a living.
我想跟你说我靠什么为生
This sicko bothering you? Because I know how to deal with weirdos.
这个神经病在骚扰你吗？ 我会对付超市之狼
I teach guys to beat the box.
我专教别人欺骗测谎器
Who are you?
你是什么人？
I teach techniques enabling anyone to beat a polygraph.
我教授的技巧可以骗过测谎器
Like special operations personnel that might be captured and interrogated.
比方从事特殊工作的人员 被逮捕必须接受审讯时
Basically, I teach people to create a new persona.
基本上，我教导人们 创造一个新的人格面貌
That way, when they lie, they're not really lying.
经我指点就真假莫辨了
- Why are you telling me this? - I don't know. But my guess is you do.
-你跟我说这些做什么？ -不知道，但我想你心里明白
Who are you? Who sent you?
你是谁？谁派你来的？
I was asked to convey this message. So you know, along with everyone else.
我负责传递讯息，通知每个人
- Good night, Mrs. Ikubik. - Yeah, get out of here.
-晚安，裘毕太太 -闪远一点
Hey, honey.
嗨，亲爱的
- Is it true? - What?
-那是真的吗？ -什么？
That you get that kind of training to beat the box?
你受过训，能骗过机器？
- What are you talking about? - The polygraph, Tom.
-什么意思？ -测谎器
Sure, but I didn't beat the box. I told the truth.
当然，但我没有骗机器 我说的是实话
- Why didn't you say you could do that? - It didn't occur to me.
-你怎么不早说？ -我没有想到
- It's not a part of who I am anymore. - That's it. How do I know who you are?
-我已经改头换面了 -你说到问题核心了，你到底是谁？
Claire, you're the only one who knows who I am.
唯有你知道我是谁
You know what? That's it. I...
知道吗？你不必再忙了…
I don't care anymore.
我不在乎了
I did it. I shot them all. Yeah.
是我干的 我开枪射死他们的
For the fun of it. Why not? Who the hell cares?
好玩嘛，有何不可 谁在乎？
The man you've woken up to every day just loves to kill women and children.
每天早上在你枕边醒来的男人 以屠杀妇孺为乐
In cold blood. Because l...
非常冷血，因为--
Who the hell knows why, Claire? Am I making any sense?
天晓得是怎么回事？ 讲得过去吗？
No.
不
I'm scared.
我很怕
This whole base ain't secure.
这基地到处被监控
They know every move we make.
他们知道我们的一举一动
Tell me. How do they know, Charlie? How do they know?
告诉我，他们怎么会知道，查理？ 他们怎么会知道？
Good question, Mrs. Kubik.
问得好，裘毕太太
- Damn! Charlie Grimes. - Hey, Renny.
-嗨，查理葛莱 -嗨，雷尼
It's been ages.
好久不见
- Did you come to beg for leftovers? - I just wanna look through your trash.
-来讨剩菜剩饭吗？ -来检查你这儿的垃圾
Okay?
好吗？
What's the problem? Take it easy. Goddamn.
怎么了？别激动，妈的
Hold his legs. Hold him.
抓着他的腿，抓住他
No, no! Please!
不，不！不要！
Come on. Come on.
走吧
- I just don't believe it. - My assistant used to say:
-我不相信 -我助手说：
"Truth is less fun than fiction."
“真相比想像无趣”
- Terry wouldn't do that. - You screw him, so you know him?
-泰瑞不会干这种事 -你睡了他就表示你了解他？
- Excuse me, Mrs. Ron Chapman. - I'm gonna sit down.
-你说什么，查普曼太太 -我要坐下
- Well, well, well. - What happened?
-哎呀 -怎么回事？
Lucy, you got a lot of explaining to do.
你可得好好解释解释
Are you all right? Who did this?
你还好吧？谁干的？
Just the old gang from down at the club.
酒吧那票狐群狗党
- The ones that know every move we make. - What are you talking about?
-那票对我们了若指掌的家伙 -你在说什么？
How do they know about the polygraph? Tarot cards?
他们怎知测谎的事？未卜先知？
Were you drinking with Waldron?
你跟华仲一起喝酒？
Every Friday, everybody drinks there. We don't talk about cases.
周五老规矩，我们没讨论案情
You were in the Corps. You know what it's like, right?
你当过兵 你知道是怎么回事，对不对？
- You can understand. - I understand you're fired.
-你知道的 -我知道你被开除了
This case will be over and you'll be gone, but I'll still be here.
案子结束你就走，我得留下来
- Did you know about this? - What?
-这件事你知不知情？ -什么？
Did you know about the attack?
你知道那袭击吗？
- You just happened to show up then? - Do you really think I would...?
-你刚好及时出现？ -你真的觉得我会--？
Let's go to the hospital. I'm worried about your ribs.
到医院去，我担心你的肋骨
Just get me ice. I've been hit before.
拿点冰来，不是第一次了
I won't be there for Hernandez. I got word. Troy Abbott got his parole.
我不是去找贺南德兹 听说特洛阿巴被假释了
I gotta go track him down.
我得去找他
Well, kind of sick.
嗯，有点恶心
Chapman taunted the victims. He tossed his gun around like a cowboy.
他像牛仔般用枪戏弄受害者
IKind of showing off. And then he executed them.
像是在卖弄技术 然后才将他们杀害
Please continue, major.
请继续说，少校
I ran to the south end of the village but it was too late.
我跑到村子南边，但太迟了
They Were all dead. Chapman Was still shooting.
全死了，查普曼还继续开枪
Get back!
退后！
Two other unit members helped me. We got him down. We got his weapon.
我和另外两人合力制止他 缴了他的械
Major, you say Sgt. Chapman did some sick things.
少校，你说查普曼有病态举止
Yet you allowed him to proceed without supervision?
你这个上司还让他先斩后奏？
I didn't know he'd take it that far.
我不知道他这么离谱
Had he been cited for this kind of behavior before?
他先前有没有因为这类行为被传唤？
No, he had not.
没有
Wasn't he your most experienced and reliable member?
他是贵单位最可靠的老手吗？
Before you answer, that's a quote from your report.
在你回答之前 这可是你自己报告上写的
- Defense Exhibit A. - Chapman was a good Marine.
-被告提出证物A -查普曼是个优秀陆战队员
- Courageous, honest. - I thought so.
-勇敢忠贞 -我同意
The kind of Marine who wouldn't go along with a cover-up...
不愿为你掩饰罪行的优秀军人…
...for you, who committed the killing. - Objection!
-于是就成了杀人犯 -抗议！
Sustained. Make that your last outburst, counselor.
有效，约束你的言辞，律师
Jury members, you are instructed to disregard that accusation.
陪审团请忽略上述指控
How's it possible that seven men, spread all over a village...
七个人散布于村子各处
...witnessed the exact same thing?
何以能目睹同一件事？
- We got to the barn at the same time. - Wow. How convenient.
-我们同时赶往该处 -哇，说得真轻松
Doesn't it make more sense that some of the witnesses were ordered to lie?
干脆说这伙人 接获指示同声说谎，还比较合理吧？
- They weren't. - How do you know?
-绝无此指示 -你怎么知道？
I'd know if that happened.
如果有此事，我一定知道
- And if that happened, you'd tell us. - Of course. I wouldn't lie.
-若此是当真，你会说出来 -会，我不会说谎
But you're trained and compelled to lie about your clandestine missions.
但你受训练去保守任务的秘密
As I understand it, you're trained to beat a polygraph.
据我所知，你还能欺骗测谎器
Is it true you possess that talent?
你有此项才能吗？
I'd only use it if interrogated by the enemy.
只有遭敌人审讯时才会使用
That's good to know.
这倒是个好消息
So tell me this, major. Do you consider me a friend?
请告诉我，少校 你把我当朋友吗？
I ain't done nothing. I didn't know there'd be pimps involved.
我没碰她 我不知道有牵扯到皮条客
You got that all wrong. That ain't me.
你搞错了，我不拉皮条
Shit, I should be so lucky.
我没那么吃得开
No, I'm just supposed to deliver this to a Troy Abbott. That you?
我只负责送这个给 特洛阿巴，是你吗？
- Yeah. Who from? - Jimmy Hernandez. Down at the base.
-是的，谁送的？ -基地的吉米贺南德兹
Hey, Charles.
嘿，查理
- What are you doing? - Got a call from the base.
-你来这干嘛？ -基地的人叫我过来
- You got a call? - Yeah.
-叫你过来？ -是的
- Bullshit. I got this call. - What, bitch? Who you raising up to?
-鬼扯，我接到电话 -你胡说什么，贱人？
- I'm tired of this bitch! - Stop!
-受不了这个贱货胡说八道！ -停止！
- Why you always in trouble? - Why you always playing daddy?
-不要再惹事了！ -不用你教训人！
- Apologize to the man. - I ain't apologi...
-向客人道歉 -我不道歉--
Do you want me to apologize, baby?
需要我道歉吗，帅哥？
Do you?
需要吗？
Gracie can apologize real good.
我道歉的方法很特别哟
Do you want me to say I'm sorry?
要我说对不起吗？对不起
So they paroled you?
他们让你假释了？
Yeah. And they bring me all the way to this dump to testify.
他们要我过来出庭作证
- What really happened down there? - I don't know. It was years ago.
-当晚到底发生什么事？ -不知道，这么多年了
El Salvador, some massacre shit.
好像在萨尔瓦多发生屠杀案
I'll bet some damn officer ordered it too.
一定是某个军官下令的
- You ain't thirsty? - Oh, yeah. Shit, yeah.
-你不渴吗？ -哦，当然
I'm just, you know, just chilling.
我只是…随意浅酌
- So then what did you say back? - What did you say?
-那你怎么回答？ -你会怎么说？
- We never get to hear shit like that. - Come on, Troy.
-我们没听过这种事 -说嘛
Who are we gonna tell, you know what I'm saying? What'd you say?
我们会跟谁说？你觉得呢？
That I was nowhere near the place.
我说我不在现场附近
They wanted me to say that I saw this guy shooting.
他们要我说目睹那家伙开枪
- Damn. - Yeah. That's intense.
-哇靠 -真强人所难
- You gonna do it? - I already did to the CID.
-你会听命行事吗？ -我已经在CID做了笔录
I just gotta testify to what I already said.
出庭只好依样画葫芦
- What's CID? - Criminal Investigative Division.
-什么是CID？ -犯罪调查部门
- Yeah, but what about this poor guy? - Forget the poor guy.
-这可怜的家伙怎么办？ -谁管他
What are you gonna do? Your XO says:
我能怎么办？顶头上司说：
"You see Chapman shoot the wetbacks?" You say, "I didn't."
“你看到查普曼枪杀当地人” 你说“没看见”
He says, "Be sure about this. Your career's on the line."
他说“想清楚，前途在你一念之间”
Everybody else said he did it. So I say what they want.
大家说他干的，我何必作梗
One more witness, no difference. Right?
多一个证人又不影响结果，对吗？
Right.
说得也是
- 911. Your address and emergency? - Yes. 10145.
-急救中心，请说出地址 -好，10145
- Is this an emergency? - Someone's trying to get in the house.
-是紧急事件吗？ -有人想破门而入
- Claire? - Hello?
-克莱儿 -喂？
- Come on. Open the door. - It's okay. I'm sorry.
-快开门 -没事了，对不起
- False alarm? - Yeah, it was a false alarm. Thanks.
-虚惊一场？ -对虚惊一场，谢谢
Charlie, you scared me to death.
查理，你吓死我了
- That guy was out there. - What guy?
-外面有人 -什么人？
- You've been drinking. - Who, me?
-你喝酒了 -我？
- Oh, my God. - Oh, no. You got it wrong.
-噢，老天 -不，你误会了
I'm just a victim of hazardous working conditions.
我是有害工作环境的受害者
- Sure you are. - Really!
-是哦 -真的
- That man was watching the house. - No, ain't nobody out there.
-有人监视这房子 -外面没有人
What is this?
这是什么？
Looks like a recorder.
是录音机吧
Is Abbott on here? Saying he never saw what he agreed to testify to in court?
有录到阿巴的声音吗？ 说他承诺出庭时将说谎？
- You didn't. - I most certainly did. You know what?
-不可能吧？ -我确定录到了
He was nowhere near the shooting. I mean, nowhere near it.
他离现场远得很 根本不在附近
Charlie, this is fabulous.
你太神了
This does it. This proves they're setting him up.
太好了，证明他是遭人诬陷
Charlie, l...
查理，我--
You really think I wanted to give up 483 days of sobriety?
你真的觉得 我会放弃483天的清醒日子？
And start all over at day one, Claire?
又重新来过吗？
- I'll make some coffee. - Wait a minute. Not so fast.
-我来煮咖啡 -等一下
See, I figure, "You already slipped, Charlie.
我想既然破戒了，查理…
So, what's one more gonna hurt?"
何妨再喝一杯？
- How about it, Claire? One for us? - I can't. I'm trying to get pregnant.
-怎么样？庆祝一下？ -不行，我正准备怀孕
Well, I'm not trying to get pregnant.
我并不想怀孕
I'm certainly not trying to get pregnant.
我当然不准备怀孕
But a judge will be...
但是法官会…
- You're late, counsel. - Prosecution requests a sidebar.
-你迟到了，大律师 -我申请休庭商议
Make it good.
你最好有好理由
- Our witness, Troy Abbott, is gone. - What?
-下位证人特洛阿巴失踪了 -什么？
- We've notified the MPs... - My ass! You let him out of jail.
-已通知宪兵-- -通知个屁，你放他出监牢的
We have a tape that impeaches Abbott's original statement.
我们有阿巴足以翻供的录音
- There's no discovery. - You got spies...
-那不在证物清单上 -你有偷窥--
- In my chambers. Court is recessed. - All rise.
-到我办公室，休庭 -起立
What are you gonna do? Your XO says:
我能怎么办？顶头上司说：
"You see Chapman shoot the Wetbacks?" You say, "I didn't."
“你看到查普曼枪杀当地人” 你说“没看见”
He says, "Be sure about this. Your career's on the line."
他说“想清楚，前途在你一念之间”
Everybody else said he did it. So I say What they Want.
大家说他干的，我何必作梗
One more Witness, no difference. Right?
多一个证人又不影响结果，对吗？
We can't authenticate this tape.
我们无法证实真伪
For all we know, he may have been coerced. It's inadmissable.
他可能被胁迫录音 不能作呈堂供证
- What? - You admitted Abbott's CID statement.
-什么？ -你们采纳了他的CID证词
We need this to rebut it. This tape exonerates Ron Chapman.
这是反证，是查普曼的无罪证据
The CID is an objective party.
CID是客观单位
Bullshit! He lied! They lied! How the hell is that objective?
胡扯！ 他、他们都说谎，何来客观？
- The tape is excluded. What's next? - Your Honor!
-录音带不能作为证物，下一步呢？ -庭上！
Excluded, counselor.
不能算，大律师！
Major.
少校
We're out of witnesses. The prosecution rests.
证人失踪，检方停止庭辩
This is a capital case. An objective judge would admit the tape!
这是项重大刑案 客观的法官会采用录音带！
- We'll hear the defense next Friday. - This is grounds for an appeal.
-被告星期五继续庭辩 -这已构成上诉条件
- Honey? We'll appeal this. - Stop. You can't fight them.
-甜心？我们一定要上诉 -打不过他们的
Don't say that. We'll get a break.
别这么说，我们另寻突破
You do not know these people. Stop it before you get yourself hurt.
你不了解这些人 未被伤害前趁早歇手
We can win this! I am not gonna let them do this to you!
我们会赢，不能让他们得逞
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
Is that a...?
那是--？
Must have done it when they installed the phones.
可能在安装电话时就装了
And you two were so ready to blame Terry. So self-righteous.
而你们却怪罪泰瑞 真是自以为是
- Go to Farrell. Demand a mistrial. - Denied.
-去找法罗，申请审判无效 -否决
There's no way to prove Waldron or Hernandez did this.
我们无法证明华仲 或贺南德兹跟此事有关
Then, what?
不然怎么办？
- We are out of witnesses and time. - Let's hear from the brigadier general.
-我们没证人也没时间了 -说不定用得上那位准将
- Not on the stand. - No.
-不会是在证人席上 -不是
- You think we should pay him a visit? - I think you should.
-我们应该去拜访他吗？ -你应该去拜访他
Why me? Are you scared of him?
为什么是我？你怕他？
No, but I'm just a thorn in the Marine Corps' ass.
不，但我是陆战队的眼中钉
But you, my dear. You're the pretty, young, sympathetic little wife.
可是，亲爱的，你是 年轻、漂亮、惹人怜爱的眷属
I don't play those games.
我不玩这种游戏
Shit.
妈的
I was starting to think that...
我开始想…
- General Marks? - No press, please.
-马克将军？ -谢绝媒体
- I'm not press. How do you do? - Ms...
-我不是媒体 -你是…
Ikubik. Claire Ikubik. I'm representing my husband, Sgt. Ron Chapman.
裘毕，克莱儿裘毕 我代表我先生朗查普曼
- Mrs. Ikubik. Good day. - General Marks.
-裘毕太太，再见 -马克将军
- You gave James Hernandez the order... - No comment.
-你命令詹姆士贺南德兹… -无可奉告
...to kill Chacon and his group.
于拉斯柯林纳杀害丹尼诺夏康
You knew they expected Detachment 27 to come under attack.
你明知27特遣队会遭到攻击
You're a dignified man. End the cover-up.
你是正直的人，不要再掩饰了
How dare you?
你胆子不小！
Your man Hernandez overreacted and opened fire.
贺南德兹反应过度，擅自开火
You are way out of line.
你简直无理取闹
Listen to this and tell me how out of line I am.
听听看我是否无理取闹
If you Wanna talk to Charlie, leave a message after the beep.
找查理，请留言
If you Wanna talk to Delilah, get your head examined.
找黛利拉，请先检查你的脑袋
The man flicked me off his suit like I was a flea.
他把我像跳蚤一般弹开
I'm gonna lose my mind. We can't let them get away with this.
我一定是昏头了 我们不能放过他们
There has to be somebody who was there. There has to be somebody...
一定有其他人在那里 一定有其他人--
- Directory assistance. - The Herald.
-查号台 -请查论坛报
Of course not. When you settle down, I do have something to say.
当然不是 你们先静下来的时候，我有话说
- Is your husband the...? - Is there a military conspiracy?
-你的先生是--？ -这是项军事阴谋？
I cannot legally comment on the details of a court-martial.
我不能正式批评军事法庭审判细节
I'd like to say emphatically that my husband is innocent.
我只能强调我先生是无辜的
There's a man Who is a stranger to me Who said last Week...
上周有个陌生人对我说
...that all laWyers are a Waste of oxygen.
律师的良心全被狗吃了
As a Wife and an attorney, I fear justice Won't ultimately be served.
身为妻子与律师 我恐怕本案之公理已荡然无存
I'd like to challenge that man or anyone With firsthand knoWledge...
我请求那个人 或任何知道一手资料…
...of What happened to come forWard.
的人站出来
To recap today's press conference With Claire Kubik...
综合今日克莱儿裘毕所言
...she's continually insisting her husband is innocent.
她坚持她丈夫是无辜的
This attorney and Wife is clearly standing by her man.
这位身兼律师的妻子力挺丈夫
Reporting live for Channel 12 NeWs, this is...
这是12号台新闻网 在现场报导，我是…
- Hello. - You just had to do it.
-你好 -你一定要那么做
- The firm just saW you on the neWs. - Hi, Alex, I've been expecting your...
-全公司都知道了 -哈罗，艾力克，我正等你的--
Claire.
克莱儿
I'll...
我会--
You, um... I'll send you my resignation tomorrow.
你-- 明天我会送辞呈过去
Claire...
克莱儿--
Get in.
上车
No.
不
Wait. Okay, wait.
等等，好吧，等我
Where are we going?
我们要去哪里？
I wanna know the truth.
我需要知道真相
I wanna know what happened at Las Colinas.
我要知道在拉斯柯林纳所发生的事
You don't care about the truth.
你根本不关心真相
All you care about is saving your husband.
你只关心怎样营救丈夫
Get out.
出来
You want to know about Las Colinas?
你想知道拉斯柯林纳的事吗？
Women like you...
跟你同样…
...beautiful...
漂亮…
...young...
年轻…
...and the old people, begging for their lives.
的女人和老年人 跪地求饶
Jesus Christ.
天啊
It was 12 years ago. They all look the same...
12年了，他们看起来都一样--
- Don't be foolish! - It's a photograph.
-别傻了！ -那是一张照片
I just want to show you a photograph.
我想给你看一张照片
I remember him. The one with the patch on his eye.
我记得他 他戴着一只眼罩
The blood still fresh from the explosion at Monte Azul.
蒙特亚萨爆炸案鲜血未干
- He was at Monte Azul? - Of course.
-他在蒙特亚萨？ -当然
He killed Danilo Chacon.
他杀了丹尼洛夏康
Chacon Was in the cafe in a secret meeting, and this man Was there.
夏康在咖啡馆开秘密会议 这个人也在那儿
He Was there.
他在那儿
That's hoW he hurt his eye.
所以他伤到眼睛
Chacon blew up the cafe and killed the Americans...
是夏康炸死咖啡馆的美国人--
You people believe anything!
你们这些人相信任何事情
They Were killed by mistake...
学生被误杀…
...because the military didn't knoW they Were there.
因为军队不知道他们在那儿
To cover it up, they blamed the rebels and pretended to look for Chacon.
为掩饰失误故意嫁祸反抗军 并假装在纳搜捕夏康
But they kneW he Was already dead, that they had killed him With the bomb.
但他们知道他早已被炸死
- Thanks a lot. - You're welcome.
-谢谢你 -不客气
- Lf it isn't Little Miss 6:00 News. - You're drunk.
-这不是六点新闻小姐吗？ -你醉了
- You were supposed to call me when... - Charlie?
-你应该打电话给我-- -查理
I called you.
我打过了
- I was out. You could've called back. - We had an agreement.
-我出去一下，你没再打 -我们有过承诺
Excuse me. I thought we had an agreement.
抱歉，我以为我们有承诺
I thought me and you was partners.
我以为你跟我是合作伙伴
- Partners don't do dumb shit... - It worked.
-合作伙伴干傻事前… -成功了
...without telling the other part of the team.
会先知会伙伴一声
- What? - I just spent an hour with the guy.
-什么？ -我刚跟那人谈了一个小时
He's the real deal. He saw the whole thing.
他才是关键，他目睹一切
Tom's innocent. This proves it.
证明汤姆是无辜的
There's a cover-up and it's bigger than we thought. I need you sober.
掩饰的罪行比我们想的还重大 你不能再喝酒了
- Come on. - All right.
-别这样 -好
- Let's get you home. - Okay, babe. All right.
-回家吧 -好吧，宝贝
- No, Charlie. - Chris, last one. Just one more.
-不要再喝了，查理 -克里斯，最后一杯
- Forget about it. - I got it. I got it.
-别理他 -我来付钱
Come on, partner.
走吧，伙伴
All right, partner.
好吧，伙伴
What the hell was that?
什么声音？
What? Oh, my God!
怎么了？不妙！
Shit, it's oil!
是机油！
Hi, sweetie.
嗨，老姐
Oh. I had the worst dream.
做了一场恶梦
I dreamt I was pregnant and these people came and took the baby away.
梦到我怀孕，婴儿被抢走
You one lucky girl.
算你命大
You and the gentleman.
你和那位先生
I want you to take something.
你该吃点药
Don't you worry about a thing. You'll have another baby.
不用担心 你可以再怀孕
What?
什么？
- Don't you worry. - What?
-不用担心 -什么？
You'll have another one.
你可以再怀孕
Jackie?
贾姬？
- No. No. - I'm so sorry.
-不 -对不起
That's not fair. No.
不公平，不
Be strong. Be strong. You have to rest.
坚强一点，坚强一点 你得休息一下
- Claire? It's Charlie. - Come in.
-我是查理 -请进
Hi.
你好
- How's your neck? - It's all right.
-脖子怎么样？ -还好
I've had worse whiplashes looking at pretty women like you on the street.
我曾在街上看像你一样美女 把扭伤脖子的更严重
I'm truly sorry, Claire.
真的很抱歉，克莱儿
I wanted that baby so much, Charlie.
我多么渴望一个孩子，查理
You know, I kept thinking...
我常想我…
...maybe there was something wrong with me or I didn't deserve it...
哪里不对，或我不配…
...or I wouldn't be a good mother.
还是我不会是个好妈妈
I really didn't think they'd do something like this.
我不敢相信他们会干这种事
- I'm at zero, Charlie. - Whoa, now.
-我心灰意冷了，查理 -噢，听我说
Listen to me. I know about zero.
听我说，我曾沉到谷底
I've hit bottom, and I was on my way back there before the accident.
我曾沉到谷底，出意外前 我又开始往下沉
But you know what?
但是你知道吗？
I think we were spared for some reason and you gotta believe that.
但是，我认为我们都逃过一劫
So for me and you, kiddo, this is day one.
所以你和我，这是刚开始
Okay?
知道吗？
You got another visitor.
你还有一个访客
Hello.
你好
Merry Christmas. You all right?
圣诞快乐，你还好吧？
I owe you an apology, lieutenant.
我该向你道歉，中尉
- We were mistaken. - That's okay.
-我们错怪你了 -没关系
Although I'm not sure "merry" is the right word to use around here.
虽然这里“快乐”不太起来
That's where you might be wrong, Mrs. Ikubik.
那可不一定，裘毕太太
Had James Hernandez injured his eye in the bombing, he'd have had treatment.
若贺南德兹在咖啡馆炸伤眼睛 他一定得接受治疗
There are covert operations records for us to look up?
有医疗记录让我们去查询？
No, he'd have insisted on it for insurance...
他需要去申请保险金…
...so the government couldn't screw him out of compensation.
以免他的补偿金被政府坑掉
- Here. - Thank you.
-拿去 -谢谢
Agent Mullins!
穆林特派员！
I just need a minute of your time.
只需要耽误你几分钟
Somehow I'm confident it's not my rugged good looks...
总不会是因为我长得帅…
...to which I owe this visit.
有幸得到你的青睐
The press accepted the story. What if Chacon didn't bomb the cafe?
媒体接受了军方的说法 但如果咖啡馆不是夏康炸的呢？
- Mrs. Ikubik... - What if Hernandez, my husband's XO...
-裘毕太太-- -如果我丈夫的上司贺南德兹…
...killed the American students by mistake?
炸咖啡馆误杀学生呢？
What if Marks, to cover it up, staged a raid on Las Colinas?
如果马克将军为了掩饰过失 故意袭击拉斯柯林纳呢？
What if all this is not my job?
如果我说这不关我的事呢？
- Just help me look into it. - Make it a lean one.
-只要帮我调查一下 -瘦肉多一点
Why not? You have your sources.
好啦，我知道你有管道
- My sources? - You say it's not your job.
-管道？ -你说那不关你的事
- I wasn't sure you were listening. - Then whose job is it?
-我以为你没在听呢 -那么是谁的事？
Come on. Whose job?
说啊，谁的事？
Goddamn, what a pain in the ass you are!
哎，你真是纠缠不休
Hernandez was injured in the explosion.
贺南德兹在爆炸中受伤
There's got to be a classified medical document somewhere.
一定有医疗资料的密件
- Charlie, it's me. - Hey, Mac.
-查理，是我 -嘿，麦克
I've been checking the rumors about hoW the Witnesses died.
我查过证人的死因
I have expenses: Phone bills, plane tickets. It'll cost you.
我跑很多地方，你准备花大钱
- You told me that. - I found the Wife of the murdered one.
-你说过了 -我找到被谋杀者的遗孀
Lisa Stenstrom is in Mexico. She sWears the military killed her husband.
住在墨西哥 她誓言她丈夫被军方谋害
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
Just inside.
在里面
- You hear from Charlie? - He called.
-有查理的消息吗？ -有
But he didn't Want to talk on the phone.
但他不愿在电话上说话
Like him, I'm not sure I should talk on the phone.
我也有同感
- He did say he Was in Mexico. - What is he doing in Mexico?
-他说他在墨西哥 -墨西哥？干嘛？
- I don't knoW. You coming back? - I'm going to L.A.
-你要回来了吗？ -对，但要先去一趟洛杉矶
- So I'll see you. - Bye.
-再见
General.
将军
You all have had him all night. It's my turn. Shall we?
你们缠他整晚了，该换我了
We uncovered the real reason you sent Detachment 27 to Las Colinas.
我们发现了你派27特遣队 到拉斯柯林纳的真正理由
- Uncovered? It's public record. - Not really.
-发现？社会大众都知道 -我看不见得
It's a matter of record that Hernandez injured his eye in Monte Azul.
记录显示 贺南德兹在蒙特亚萨炸伤眼部
He was seen in the truck from which the grenade was thrown.
有人看到他 在手榴弹被丢出的卡车上
He was treated at a hospital in San Salvador before Las Colinas.
到拉斯柯林纳前曾在首府就医
Your gung-ho raid was a decoy for your bombing.
袭击旨在混淆炸弹事件
This fairy tale of yours would have to be based...
尽管你用机密文件编童话
...on classified material, even if any of it were remotely possible.
但还是毫无可信度
Now, you're bluffing. And you're doing it badly.
你吹牛的工夫不够高明
Thank you.
谢谢
We'd be only too happy to have you testify under oath...
我们很乐意让你出庭
...and allow the court to fully explore our evidence.
让法庭测底检查我们的证据
For example, classified document dated 3/14/88. Hernandez's medical report...
譬如，88年3月15的密件 贺南德兹…
...for a shrapnel wound at Santa Maria Hospital.
在圣塔玛丽亚医院的就医记录
That's the same day and mighty close to Monte Azul.
就在同一天 那也很接近蒙特亚萨
You have no shame. Look what you're willing to do to free a murderer.
你真是寡廉鲜耻 不择手段为凶手脱罪
The charges get dropped or the document goes public.
撤销告诉或是密件被曝光
Haven't you noticed that you've been unlucky lately?
你有没有注意到近来你诸事不顺？
Now, caution might be the order of the day for you.
小心乃上上之策啊
I am not afraid of you.
我不怕你
I've survived you once, you smug son of a bitch.
我活过来了，放冷箭的小人
The real question is, will you survive me?
问题是…你逃得过我这关吗？
Make it go away, general, or the document goes public.
撤销告诉不然我让密件曝光
For both our sakes, sir.
为你我双方着想，先生
Pull over. Right here!
停车
Jackie. Jackie?
贾姬？
- Ma'am. - Claire? You all right?
-女士 -克莱儿？你没事吧？
Oh, my God. Yeah.
噢，老天，我没事
What's that about?
怎么回事？
Colonel Farrell wants us in court tomorrow at 0800.
法罗要我们明天8点出庭
Waldron filed a motion to have you disqualified from the case...
华仲申请免除你的辩护资格
...for talking to the press.
因为你向媒体放话
Any word from Charlie?
查理有消息吗？
I've been trying his cell all day. Just getting voice mail.
打了一整天，只有语音信箱
We've still got Hernandez's medical report.
我们有贺南德兹的就医资料
I'll... I'll do my best.
我会尽力而为
Farrell wouldn't admit a classified document any more than the Abbott tape.
法罗不会接受密件作为证物
- Maybe you should take the deal. - There's no more deal. Not now.
-或许你应该接受减刑协商 -没有协商机会了
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Ikubik. - Why don't you spend the night out?
-抱歉，裘毕太太 -你们为何不出去过夜？
I don't know if it's a good idea to be here tonight.
今晚可能不太方便
I could use a little time on my own.
我利用机会静一静
- Hey. You heard from Charlie? - No.
-有查理的消息吗？ -没有
- What's going on, honey? - I don't know.
-怎么回事？ -我不知道
All rise.
起立
Be seated.
请坐
Major Waldron, Mrs. Ikubik, please approach.
华仲少校和裘毕太太请上前
What is this?
这是怎么回事？
For reasons of national security, the Department of Defense decided...
因国家安全理由，国防部下令
...the charges against Sgt. Ron Chapman are to be withdrawn.
撤销对查普曼上士的告诉
Court is closed. Sgt. Chapman, you're free to go.
结案 查普曼上士，你自由了
Oh, my God.
感谢老天
Hey, Charlie. Listen, in case you're interested, pal...
查理，如果你有兴趣知道…
...we won.
我们赢了
We're going to Marin. We're blowing this town.
我们离开这里到马林去了
If you want to call, that's where we'll be. Hope you're okay.
你可以打电话到那里 希望你平安无事
Jesus, look at this.
天啊，你们看
What do you suggest I do?
我该怎么办？
Have Jackie meet us on the next block. Will there be more at the airport?
叫贾姬开车到下一个街口来接我们 机场会有更多吗？
- Probably. - Why bother? Let's just drive.
-可能 -不要麻烦了，我们继续吧
Thank you.
谢谢
- You take care of yourself. - You too.
-保重 -你也一样
Okay. Thanks, Jackie.
多谢
- Well, kid, turns out you're okay. - Well, you too, kid.
-你还不差嘛 -你也不错
- Thank you so much. - Thank you, lieutenant.
-很谢谢你 -多谢，中尉
We're gonna take our time.
我们慢慢开啦
We'll call you when we get there. Probably around 7?
我到了会打个电话，可能7点吧？
- Bye.
-再见
A week before Paul was murdered, he called an old Marine Corps buddy...
保罗遇害前一个礼拜 他跟部队老同事通过电话
...who, incidentally, was killed about two months after Paul.
很巧对方两个月后也遇害
I don't know what they talked about, but it upset him.
不知道他们说什么，他很激动
You have no idea what it's like to see a loved one killed in front of you.
看着心爱的人遇害 真是难受
You believe this is connected to the military?
你认为此事跟军方有关？
Yeah.
没错
It's just a feeling, because Paul knew him. You know?
只是一种感觉 因为保罗认识凶手
He just seemed to recognize him. That thing he did with the hands.
他似乎认识他，他的手势
Paul seemed to know who he was.
保罗好像知道他是谁
You think that owl's still around here?
你猜猫头鹰还在附近吗？
You know what bothered me more than anything?
知道什么最令我烦恼吗？
I couldn't protect you.
不能保护你
I had to stand by while they hurt you.
他们伤害你时 我束手无策
I need more champagne.
我该多买几瓶香槟
I love you.
我爱你
I thought you unplugged that.
我以为你拔下电话线
I did, but I tried Charlie one more time.
是啊，但后来我又拨给查理
- Hi, Claire. It's me. - Sweetheart, I'm sorry.
-克莱儿，是我 -亲爱的，对不起
- Look, I'm... - I'll be right back.
-听着，我 -我马上回来
I'm sorry I Wasn't there today. I didn't mean to let you doWn.
抱歉我今天缺席 我不是故意让你失望
Yeah, Charlie.
是的，查理
Look, Claire. I'm real sorry. I couldn't get there.
抱歉，我真的赶不回去
Why today? Of all days. What if Marks had opted to testify, or what...?
为什么一定是今天？ 万一马克愿意出庭怎么办？
You know what? I don't want to talk about it.
知道吗？ 我不想再谈这事了
I thought I had a friend.
我还以为我交到一个朋友
I am your friend.
我是你的朋友啊
Sure you are.
当然
Say a toast for my husband while you drink.
喝醉之前顺便敬汤姆一杯
- Goodbye, Charlie. - Listen. I am your friend.
-再见，查理 -听我说，我是你的朋友
I was being your friend today. More than you'd care to know.
我比你预期中的还够朋友
- What do you mean? - We need to talk.
-什么意思？ -我们得谈谈
I just don't think that now's a good time for it.
但现在不太适合
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I think AA meetings are supposed to be anonymous.
戒酒会不是都隐姓埋名？
- I'm gonna get more champagne. - Hurry back.
-我去买香槟 -快去快回
Are Marks and Hernandez gonna give us trouble?
马克和贺南德兹还想找麻烦？
- Tom still there? - He's going to the store.
-汤姆还在吗？ -他去买东西了
All right, get to your computer. Pull up your calendar.
你查一下电脑里的行事历
Find out Where your husband Was on January 20, 1997.
1997年1月20日汤姆在哪里？
- Why are you doing this? - Look it up. It's important.
-为什么要查？ -快查，很重要
He was in Santa Fe. He met a collector. I picked him up from the airport.
到圣塔菲见收藏家 我去机场接他
February 10, '97.
1997年2月10日呢？
Houston, Texas. Trade show.
德州休士顿的贸易展
Claire, listen to me. Those are the dates that witnesses were murdered.
克莱儿，证人在这些日子被杀
Stenstrom Was murdered January 20, 1997 in Santa Fe, NeW Mexico.
史丹斯壮97年1月20日 在新墨西哥圣塔菲遇害
Allen died in Houston, Texas, February 10.
亚伦在2月10日死于休士顿
Hernandez said that Tom tossed his gun back and forth, taunting his victims.
贺南德兹说 汤姆来回抛枪戏弄被害人
- Is he ambidextrous? - Yeah.
-他能双手并用？ -对
Stenstrom's wife said the man shot her husband...
史丹斯壮的太太说凶手…
...then tossed the gun back and forth, shoWing off...
来回抛枪…
...and shot him again With the other hand.
然后换手开枪
- I can't talk about this right now. - Sure.
-我现在没办法跟你谈 -好
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I just thought I ought to let you knoW.
抱歉，我认为应该让你知道
Fine. I've got to go.
好，我该挂电话了
I thought you went to the store.
你不是去买东西？
I grabbed the wrong keys.
拿错了钥匙
Those are the right keys. Those are Jackie's.
钥匙没错啊 这是贾姬的
- What are you working on? - Nothing.
-你在忙什么？ -没什么
- You want to run out to get champagne? - I'm not in the mood.
-一起去吗？ -我没心情喝香槟
- Ouch, Tom. - I'm sorry.
-好痛，汤姆 -对不起
Well, let's just talk, then.
那么，我们来谈谈吧
Talk about what?
谈什么？
About what you were talking about on the phone.
谈刚刚电话里谈的事情
What, you think I'm stupid, Claire? You must.
你当我是呆子吗，克莱儿？
Why not talk to me about it? You like to keep secrets with Grimes.
为什么不找我谈？ 喜欢跟葛莱保有秘密？
Your life is one big secret.
你的生活就是个大谜团
Did you do it, Tom?
是你干的吗？汤姆
You can tell me.
你可以跟我说
I certainly have a right to know.
我有权利知道
Risked my life for it. Lost a baby.
我为你冒过生命危险 流掉一个孩子
Did you kill those people?
你有没有杀害那些人？
Yes.
有
I did.
我干的
I had to. That's what I was trained to do, Claire.
逼不得已 那正是我所接受的训练
They lied to me. They told me they were terrorists.
他们骗我 跟我说他们是恐怖份子
They told me to interrogate them.
上头要我讯问他们
And so you do What you have to do to get every...
于是我不择手段…
...any kind of information you can out of them, and so I did.
以取得必要的情报 于是我就动手
Because I was the best at it. And they knew it.
因为我是顶尖高手 长官们也知道这点
- What about Stenstrom and Allen?
-史丹斯壮和亚伦呢？ -他们怎么样？
Stenstrom saw me on the street one day...
史丹斯壮有一天撞见我
...and he told Allen. And they needed to go away, you see?
又跟亚伦说，所以必须除掉
Do not look at me like that!
不要那样看我
I do not deserve it.
你没资格藐视我
Sorry.
对不起
I've been tired.
我太累了
I was just protecting us. We'll get over this. You'll see.
我只是想保护我们
Honey?
甜心？
Stop it! Stop it!
住手！住手！
Oh, God, you're hurting me. You're hurting me.
天啊！你弄痛我了！你弄痛我了！
You're hurting me. You're hurting me.
你弄痛我了！你弄痛我了！
Tom, stop it!
汤姆！住手！
Tom, look at me, look at me. Honey, honey.
汤姆，看着我
Shut up, shut up. You're a liar. Liar. Don't lie to me.
闭嘴！你这骗子！不要骗我！
Liar.
骗子！
I didn't want to have to do this to you, Claire.
我也不希望这么做
Tom.
汤姆
It's okay.
别激动
I'm sorry.
对不起
From Santa Cruz to Walnut Creek, San Rafael to Salinas...
从圣塔克鲁斯到胡桃溪 从圣罗菲尔到莎林纳…
...Oakland to San Francisco, you're listening to the number one station...
从奥克兰到旧金山 这是报导体育…
...for sports, neWs and information.
新闻和时事的最棒电台
You have a whole suite of offices.
办公室很大哟
Yeah, but don't talk about it because I might get spooked.
别提了，我会怕
I mean, who knows what might happen?
谁知道会发生什么事情？
How are you holding up?
近来好吗？
I'm okay.
我没事
- Same old associate? - Oh, yeah.
-同样的合伙人？ -是啊
She's back there in the back somewhere.
她在后面某个地方
I brought her a bone back from lunch, so she's probably busy.
午餐帮她带了根骨头 所以她很忙
Hello. Come see me. You're beautiful.
你好，来看我 你很漂亮
Hello.
你好
You know, I often ask myself why I never left San Lazaro.
常问自己为何不离开圣拉萨罗
It occurred to me that I never left because I didn't have anyplace to go.
因为我根本没地方可以去
You know, it could read Grimes and Ikubik.
事务所可以叫“葛莱与裘毕”
It's got to say Grimaldi.
不，要叫“葛莱摩尔迪”
My maiden name. And, Charlie, you gotta do something about these colors.
那是我婚前的姓而且 墙壁颜色得换掉
Well, I'm very sensitive about my work environment.
我对工作环境很敏感
Really? So?
真的？
I was thinking about a tropical color, with a contrasting print.
我考虑用热带颜色 窗框则用对比色
Claire!
克莱儿！
Check out this exterior. It's skid-row chic, I understand that.
外面很有贫民窟风格，我了解
But the watermarks gotta go. That's a given.
但是，水渍一定要去除掉